確認する 旅団員パクノダ　本人だな？ もちろん。 本当よ。
Leol has chased Morel into
an underground church, where they will now fight one another.
それを厳守すれば リーダーは解放する。
This ability only activates when it rains. Inamura!
まずは　リーダーへの条件。
Return x And x Retire
１つ　今後　念能力の使用を 一切　禁じる。 ２つ…。
My Inamura
本当に　これでいいのか？ 奴らの頭さえ潰せば
Well? Aren't my big waves rad?
「クモ」は瓦解する そう思っていた しかし… ((俺に人質としての 価値などない))
I can easily wash away your wimpy smoke!
頭をとっても　「クモ」は動く リーダーが絶対なのではない
You're having trouble moving
in the water, right?
場合によっては 頭さえ切り離す集団
You like how easily my board can maneuver?
それが　「幻影旅団」！
If you stand still, I'll give you a quick death.
ここでリーダーの動きを 封じたところで
That's not your ability.
奴らを封じることはできない
It belongs
かといって 他に　てはあるか？
to my buddy!
ない！　見つからない…
Oh, making a boat of smoke?
そう　これでいいんだ…
So he can stand on that smoke?
２人を取り戻す それが最優先！
You think that's enough to defeat my waves? I told you, that's not your ability!
もう　仲間を失うのは 絶対に嫌だ！ ２つ　今後　旅団員との 一切の接触を絶つこと。
This one is my own original...
この律する小指の鎖 「ジャッジメントチェーン」を リーダーに刺す。
Tornave!
次は　お前だ　パクノダ。
I stop my opponent's
movements with a whirlpool.
１つ　今夜０時までに ゴンとキルアを
Here I go! Then, I finish him with a harpoon from above!
小細工なしで 無事に解放すること。 ２つ　私のことについて 一切　情報を漏らさぬこと。
My harpoon can match the speed of sound, and pierce a whale at the very bottom
of the ocean, even from the sky!
異存がなければ お前にも鎖を刺す。
Take this!
あっ！
He disappeared?
もし　ゴンとキルアが　操作系の 能力者に操られているとしたら
Impossible! The whirlpool should have incapacitated him.
心音で　それを察知できるか？ 可能よ。
He had no way to escape.
いつもと　どう違うかは 聞き分けられるわ。
Bastard...
十分だ。
How did you do it?
人質交換の前に 言っておくことがある。
I simply exhaled.
クラピカ…
When it comes to lung capacity,
no one in the world beats me.
あなたは頭の隅で 矛盾を感じている パクノダが　なぜ１人で来たのか そのことに
He used his breath as jet propulsion
to break out of the whirlpool?
「旅団」が本当に 非情なだけの組織なら
Okay, it's my turn now!
この人質交換自体 成立しないはず
It's your turn?
((追い詰められているのは お前達のほうだ))
In this battle, you don't get a turn!
彼らは　鉄の掟を作り
All you get to do is drown in my waves!
団長は　それを 順守しようとしている でも　団員は？
During this exchange, I've learned three things.
少なくとも彼女は違う
First, I now know your power.
あなたが憎しみを 絞り出すようにしながら 見据えている　その女性は
Somehow, you're able to use
other people's abilities.
今　あなたと同じ理由で そこに立っているのよ
And those earphones have nothing to do with your power.
ただ　仲間を…
They're either for show or for luck.
団長を救いたい一心で…
Or it means someone is sending you orders.
あなたは　それに 気づいているのでしょ？ まず　お前は仲間の元に戻り 人質交換の旨を伝える。
If he meant to impair his hearing
to strengthen his power, he shouldn't be able to hear me talk.
そして　０時までに２人を連れて リンゴーン空港に来い。
What's the third thing?
仲間は連れて来るな どこに行くかも言うな。
Your lifespan. That Inamura ability belongs
to a Hunter named Grachan.
分かったわ　交渉成立ね 空港へ送ってちょうだい。
You probably encountered and defeated
him when he was sent
なぜ　何も聞かない。
I'll punish you for stealing my buddy's ability!
私が何者か分かってるんだろう？ 不安じゃないのか？
Your life ends today!
理不尽な交渉だと思わないか？
Hold on... That's a totally one-sided misinterpretation.
私が本当に リーダーを返すと思うか？
I was protecting myself from humans
who were hunting me down.
ええ。
It was self-defense.
あなたに　だます気があるなら わざわざ そんなこと聞かないでしょ？
And I didn't steal his ability.
のめると思ってるのか そんな条件をよ。
That's an excuse thieves use.
場所を言え　パクノダ。
Well, arguing with you is pointless.
ガキ２人を殺して 鎖野郎をやりに行く。 どうしても？ どうしてもだ。
I'd like to get my hands on his ability, but defeating him is more important.
言わないなら 行かせるわけにはいかねえ。 絶対に場所は言わないし ２人を連れて戻るのは私だけよ
Right now, our top priority
is to defeat one another.
邪魔しないで。
I'll repeat myself...
邪魔!?　そりゃ　どっちの話だよ コラ　あ!?
I'm sorry, but you don't get a turn!
行きなよ　パクノダ ここは　あたし達が止める。 止める？　ナメてるか？
Big Wall! Giant Wave
Big Wall
お前ら　頭どうかしちまったのか？
I'm flooding this underground church. My wall of water's gonna suck you in!
恐らく　私達　着く前に 全員　鎖野郎にやられてるね。
Just try and find your way to the surface!
本当に分からないの？ あ？
Now, will he make it up?
パクノダが　なぜ　お前達に何も話さず 戻ろうとしているのか。
Will I smash his skull with my board? Launch my harpoon through his gut?
マチが　なぜ　お前達を 止めようとしているのか。
Which do I choose?
本当に操られてるからって 思ってんの!? お前達の団長を助けたいからに 決まってるだろ！
Either way, if he shows his face above water, he's done.
仲間を取り戻したいって気持が そんなに理解できないのか！ 黙ってろ　ガキが！ 助かりたくって必死か？
He isn't coming back up... Has he drowned?
自分のために 言ってるんじゃ　ない。 取り消せ！
No, he was confident about his lung capacity.
やれやれ。
That means he can survive for
ten or twenty minutes.
嫌なこった 文句あるなら来いよ。
No, wait. It's just possible
一歩でも動いたら その首　へし折るぜ。 じゃ　嫌だね！　誰が動くもんか！
that he's able to remain underwater like a whale!
もしも お前達と約束を交わしたのなら
There you are!
それを一方的に破ることも 絶対しない！
Don't move!
それは　直接会ったパクノダには 分かったはずだ。
I'll impale you with my harpoon.
条件通りにすれば 団長は必ず戻って来る！
Bubbles on the opposite side, too?
勝手なこと ゴチャゴチャ吹きやがって！
And over here! And over there!
もう　やめろ。
There are air bubbles everywhere...
シャル　今　俺達にとって 最悪のケースってのは　何だ？
It's possible, if he formed his smoke
into a hose with multiple branches.
うん… 団長が　すでに死んでて
That way, he wouldn't give away his position.
パクノダ達が操作されている。
Hey! How long are you gonna stay under?
鎖野郎の所在は　結局　知れず この２人にも まんまと逃げられる…　かな。
Do you expect me to give up and drain the water?
それが間違ってんだよ。
No, that isn't it!
最悪なのは　俺達全員がやられて 「クモ」が死ぬことだ。
The bubbles are camouflage! Is he running?
それに比べりゃ お前が言ったケースなんざ 屁みてぇなもんだ　違うか？
If his lung capacity is that great, it's possible
ん…　まぁ　そうだね。
he could swim out through the maze of
underground corridors leading down here.
理由はどうであれ　お前ら どっちも団長に　より過ぎだぞ。
I can't let him escape!
その結果 「旅団」が致命的に崩壊してみろ。 それが団長に対する 一番の裏切りだろうが。
I told Welfin and Brovada to stay out of this,
so I could take all the credit...
このまま　もめてたら そうなりかねねえぞ　頭冷やせ。
My head's spinning?
いいじゃねえか　好きにさせて。
And my chest hurts...
ガキとパクノダを行かせて もし団長が戻って来なかったら
Have I been poisoned?
簡単なことだろうが。
My board disappeared?
それでいいよ それで気が済むならね。
Is it because my physical and
mental stability are compromised?
まぁ　あたしゃ操られてないし 簡単に　やられもしないけど。
Can't move...
チッ。
Can't breathe...
[TEL] もしもし。 [TEL]　人質の２人に代われ。
My power stopped working,
but the water hasn't gone away?
壊すなよ！
Because we're underground?
[TEL]　大丈夫か？　奴らは　いるか？
Crap...
うん　全員いるよ。 おい！
I let him think he had the advantage
so I could turn the tables on him.
チッ…　そっちの条件通り…。
But it looks as though the one
who was backed into a corner...
追わなくていいのか？ これで　もう鎖野郎が
was me...
うるせぇ　追おうとすりゃ また　お前らが止めるだろうが。
Am I gonna die?
とりあえず　様子見ててやるよ。 もし　これで団長が 戻って来なかったら てめぇも　ぶっ殺すからな。
Am I... Am I gonna die here?
[TEL]　止まっている飛行船に乗れ 行き先は　もう伝えてある。
So he was using smoke hoses
約束通り　３人ね。
to send air bubbles everywhere.
飛び立つまでは分からない 周りを注意してくれ。
But what kind of...
あっちから人が来る！
poison did he use?
[TEL]
That was faster than I expected.
あれは！　ヒソカ！
The poison you've inhaled is lethal.
[TEL]　やぁ。 何で来たのよ！
But it's something naturally found in air.
[TEL]　抜け出して来たのか!? 安心しなよ 影武者を置いて来ているから。
Carbon dioxide. Morel used his immense lung capacity
針なしで顔変えると　４５時間で 元に戻っちゃうから… [TEL]　何をたくらんでる？ 僕も　こいつに乗せてくれ。
to suck in the stagnant air trapped in the church, and exhaled it with an increased
concentration of carbon dioxide.
断ったら　この場で ゴンとキルアを殺しちゃうかな？
I started my attack
[TEL]　貴様…！ なんて…　そんな もったいないことしないけど
before you ever began.
僕のターゲットは　団長のみ。 彼が解放されれば 僕も船を降りるよ。
If he was telling the truth, Grachan should be getting his ability back.
キルア　ケータイを胸に当てろ。
I have a few hours in which to move around.
大丈夫　何もされてないわ。
During that time, I must see
them with my own eyes!
よし！　交換開始だ！
I've observed Bizeff's movements
with my crystal ball.
存分に味わうがいい
They are...
出発していいそうだ。 そう。
But...
そうそう 実は　僕の本当の占いでは 団長とのデートは 火曜日のはずで
Oh? How are you feeling?
団員は半分になってる はずだったんだ。
Octopus! Where am I?
運命は　少しずつ　ずれて来ている。
How long was I out? Don't call me an octopus!
ううん　団長に鎖を刺せたんだね。
This is an underground clinic for folks
with roots in the underworld.
ああ　だが　これで 全てが解決したわけではない。
You were out for two whole days. Two days?! I need to get going! Hey!
ニャ。
You need a few days before— Oh, you're awake?
団長は？ ここには来られない。
That's great. Thanks for everything you've done.
あ!?　ふざけろよ きっちり説明しろ！
I'm checking out now. Not until you pay me.
返答次第じゃ…。
Your total bill comes to 1.8 million Jenny.
大丈夫　その代わり…。
If you can't pay, I'll take body parts instead.
１度に撃てる弾は６発
I don't have my wallet on me.
I'll wire it to you when I get back.
ちょうど　結成時のメンバー分
I'm not stupid enough to trust
that you'll keep that promise.
フェイタン　フィンクス マチ　ノブナガ
Until you find someone to bring
the money, you're staying here.
シャルナーク　フランクリン。
I don't have time for that!
信じて　受け止めてくれる？
It costs 10,000 Jenny per minute. Would you just shut up and go away?
まさか…　パク！
Hello? Hey, it's me.
おい！ お前　やっぱり奴に操作され…。
Killua! Where are you? Are you okay?
フィンクス！
What happened?
信じろ　あれはパクだ。
I'll explain when I see you.
私の記憶　私の思い
A strong enemy gave me some trouble. I've been in the hospital. Oh... Well, I'm glad you called. This means you're okay now, right?
全て込める
Yeah, I'll be back soon. Anything happen on your side?
ハッ…
We have a plan that could
defeat the King if it goes well.
お願い…
Oh...
私で…　終わりに…
We should meet, so I can hear what you think. Okay.
パク…。
Then, I need you to send money
to a certain bank account.
死んでる…。
That just leaves Palm.
どういうこと？
You haven't been able to reach her?
俺が説明する。
No. She's probably still in the palace...
全て分かった。
But wouldn't that mean Neferpitou's
Nen has already exposed her?
パクノダは…。
I imagine she's in the warehouse,
beneath the palace.
クラピカの熱 このまま下がらないといいのにね。 そうだな。 …って　おい！ 今　すごいこと言っただろ！
Pitou's En can't reach that far. But since the exit is in the
palace, she can't get out.
クラピカは　もう　「旅団」と 闘っちゃダメな気がするんだ。
How's Knov-san doing?
えっ？
Well...
クラピカから能力のこと聞いた時 思ったんだ。
he's probably out of this fight.
もっと別の能力に してたんじゃないかって。 そうかな？
But he did manage to place the exits.
だって 本当に相手を殺そうと思ったら
There's no change to our plan.
心臓に鎖を打ち込むなんて 回りくどいやり方しないでしょ？
Three days to go...
１人　捕まえても すぐには殺せないよ。 他の仲間のこととか 聞かなきゃなんないしさ。
His wounds are already healed!
そっか…。
No problem.
でも最初は　そうだったとしても 今のクラピカは　もう…
Okay, I confirmed receipt of the money.
)
You can leave. Right now.
団長が戻らなきゃ 奴ら　今まで以上に 必死でクラピカ捜すだろうし。
What are you doing? Let's go.
うん…。
Huh?
俺達も オークション会場に行く時は
We're gonna join my buddies.
細心の注意を払わないと。
I'll introduce you.
『グリードアイランド』に関する 秘策ってのはよ！
But...
お前の作戦頼みなんだぞ！ うん…　でも　確率は五分五分だよ。
Well, I won't force you.
最初　７０％とか 言ってなかったか？
I'll just tell you this. Thank you.
なるほど　そりゃ面白い。
Uh, wait...
…っていうか それしかないって感じだな。
Actually...
現実的で　かつ堅実。
It's okay if I come?
うん　五分五分どころか ８割方　成功する！
I mean, I'm just a...
ホント!? ああ　行けるぜ！
What?
オークション会場は Ｂホールだって。
Was I the only one who thought
we were already friends?
お！
It's really... okay?
えっ？ えっ？
It isn't about what's okay. It's whether you're coming or not.
何で奴らが　ここにいんのさ!? 知るかよ！
I'm going! I'm going with you!
逃げるっつうの！
I want to make something clear.
安心するね 別に　お前達やるつもりないよ。
The next time something like this happens, I won't bother thanking you.
今となったら鎖野郎を やるわけにもいかなくなったしな。 えっ　どういうこと？ あぁ？ 団長に「念」の鎖　刺したんだろ？
So if something happens,
and I end up helping you, you don't need to thank me.
じゃあ 殺せるわけねえじゃねぇか。 何で？　逆じゃないの？
Friends are supposed to help friends.
こういう時　便利だよなぁ 素直に聞ける　こいつの性格
From now on, we'll be working together. So we'll be helping each other.
「念」ってのは　死ねば消えるとは 限らねえんだよ。
Supporting each other isn't a big deal.
深い恨みや 未練を持ったまま死ぬと その「念」は　強く残る。 残された「念」は
It'd be lame to thank each other
for every little thing.
憎悪や執着の対象へ おのずと向かう。
Yeah, this is it.
そうなると 念能力を使えねえ団長は
This is the world I wanted.
その邪念を　もろに受けて 心身をやられちまう恐れがある。
The world I longed for and sought...
それほど　死者の「念」は強い。
But deep down, I thought
it was beyond my reach...
だから　鎖野郎をやるわけには…。
That it wasn't meant for me...
And wouldn't happen...
分かってるよ これ以上　言わねえよ
I thought it wasn't meant to be...
除去できる者がいる ってことはな
Killua, I'm... I'm so happy, I could die!
東か…。
Huh? Why are you crying?
まっ　そんなわけで　俺達は お前らから手を引く。
Because... Because you're doing this for me!
今日は　純粋に 競売を楽しみに来ただけだ。
Come on...
他の連中は ホームに戻る気だしな。
I want to make one more thing clear.
あの…　パクノダさんは？
The world you're stepping into is far more brutal
あいつは死んだよ。
than the world of the Chimera Ants.
そう…。
They may seem similar, but there's a huge difference between
risking a life and throwing it away.
((手負いの私からなら 逃げられるはずでしょ))
People staring death in the face every day
((そしたら　こっちの切り札は なくなって
don't want to hear that someone's ready to die.
鎖野郎は　望み通り 団長を殺せるのに 何で　そうしないの？ あいつの仲間なんでしょ？)) )
Only people who maintain a daily
regimen to stay in tip-top shape, and can swallow just enough poison to
fall short of a lethal dose, get to survive.
((仲間だから　本当はクラピカに 人殺しなんてしてほしくない))
That's how it goes.
((だから　交換で済むなら それが一番いいんだ))
Are you ready to join us?
どうしたの？ 早く行こうぜ。
the words I most wanted to hear?
パクは　お前らに感謝してたぜ。
A foolish question. I see paradise before me.
次回　物語は
I've seen the other side...
グリードアイランド編へと 動き出す
I've made contact.